Hi, my name is Nicholas Maloney and welcome to Aurate, a tool that helps teachers and speech pathologists create interactive phonon learning activities.
currently choose between 2, Wordle or Word Search.
Let's go check out Wordle.
Here you can select from 5 different words, three different difficulties and enable or disable hints.
Currently, this live preview also reflects the downloaded HTML document and provides colors that represent correct, almost correct, or incorrect answers.
Downloading the HTML, we receive our standalone activity, which maintains all the coloring and functionality of the live preview,
well as a restart button for the student or learner to redo the activity.
Moving to the word search
style.
Three difficulty options, the ability to enable or disable hints,
There is also a regenerate puzzle button which allows you to regenerate the puzzle, changing the locations of the given characters, but also denotes it with a seed so educators can regenerate the same puzzle in the future if it was a successful activity.
Downloading this HTML file downloads the standalone activity and maintains all color and functionality, including a restart button.
An important thing to note
is
Changing between light and dark mode changes
the theme of the activity downloaded.
For instance, if we change to light mode and redownload the Wordle activity,
downloaded will be in light mode, of course, still maintaining the theme and functionality of the same activity in dark mode.
And that concludes the demonstration for Auray.
Thank you.